Lingling.
I found where the door is.
Really?
Then let's run.
But the stone door has a mechanism.
I haven't found where it is yet.
I know where the mechanism is.
Where?
I can tell you.
But when you escape,
you must take me with you.
Don't worry.
After I get out,
I will bring the police to save you.
What if you run away and don't come back?
Take me with you.
I don't want to die here.
I will definitely come back to save you.
No whispering.
Get back to work.
We are from the Phoenix Police Department.
A wanted criminal ran here.
Did you see him?
We didn't see him.
Search.
I'd like to see who dares.
Officer.
Are you going to search my uncle's house
for no reason?
Uncle.
Don't be afraid.
With us here,
no one dares to touch a hair on your head.
You dare to openly oppose the police department.
Do you know the consequences?
Where is it?
The exit is right there.
I thought you really wanted to leave here.
I didn't expect your awakening
to be just a tool for someone else's dirty work.
I knew
you wouldn't give up.
Let's see where
you can run this time.
Senior Sister.
Violating the sect's rules
should be publicly tried by the Venerable.
You can't use private punishment.
This is what the Venerable told me to do.
This time,
don't even think about using it again.
Trying to fool me with the trick of the Heavenly Lord's possession.
No.
Siyao.
Don't move.
Are you okay?
How is it?
Did you find any clues?
Come with me.
Don't move.
You really are the envoy sent by the Heavenly Lord.
You must remember,
it's not over yet.
Report.
Come in.
Superintendent Li.
This is
an urgent letter sent by Special Envoy Huang.
What happened?
Huang Xianzhong bypassed Zeng Guoquan
and applied to the headquarters for Jiang Siyao's promotion.
Then is Jiang Siyao no longer suspended?
The suspension investigation letter issued by the city government
doesn't need to be reported to the headquarters.
But the orders from the headquarters
must be executed by our police station.
Then...
What position is she promoted to?
Superintendent,
in charge of operations.
Who has a higher rank between you two?
She does.
What is your original name?
I forgot.
Forgot?
How long have you been in the Jingxiang Society?
The exact time,
I don't remember either.
Then why did you help the people of the Jingxiang Society
persecute others?
I was forced.
If I didn't do this,
I would be beaten,
locked up,
and burned to death.
Then,
who founded this organization?
It's the Master.
The Master?
Who is the Master?
I don't know who he is either.
He always wears a mask.
I have never seen his true face.
Besides wearing a mask,
is there anything else special about him?
He
only appears at the base to preach
on the 15th of every month.
But he didn't come this month.
Let me ask you.
My necklace,
is it in your hands or not?
I put it in the storehouse that night.
I didn't touch it.
You still have a chance to turn over a new leaf.
What is it?
Who is the Teaching Venerable?
And,
why do the villagers of Baxian Village keep his secret?
Okay.
I will tell you
everything I know.
Can you stop taking risks alone?
Isn't that what being a cop is about?
You're a cop now too.
I'm not talking about the job.
You're avoiding me.
I'm not.
Jiang Siyao.
Do you have nine lives?
Ye Shi'an.
On my wedding day, my fiancé
died tragically,
and then my father passed away too.
I only have one belief in my heart,
which is to find the real killer
and avenge them.
So?
So don't waste your time
on me.
Even for revenge, you shouldn't
throw your life away.
You have things you want to do.
I have things I want to do too.
Then you don't need to worry about me anymore.
Sir.
Yao.
This time,
you really made a great contribution.
If it weren't for your strategizing
and restoring my position,
I wouldn't have solved this case
so smoothly.
This case has already
caused a huge uproar.
The General Bureau has issued an official document
demanding a thorough investigation.
I will not let you down.
That's why I asked the General Bureau
to advance your promotion.
Now the foreigners and churches in the concession
also want to intervene in this case.
They will send someone to contact you immediately
for a joint investigation.
Once this case involves foreigners,
the problem will be very serious.
In this chaotic world,
sometimes
you have to learn to play dumb.
Sir,
are you saying...
In Lei Lie's case,
Li Chengrui definitely has some problems.
But
in the Jingxiang Society case,
he was willing to step in
and save you from trouble.
Ayao,
he who chases the deer
does not see the hare.
I will put up with him.
Because I always feel that behind him
there is a big shot.
Extra! Extra!
Ta Kung Pao front page headline.
Fenghuang Police Station busted a mysterious organization.
Extra, extra!
You were so cool this time, Senior.
Even Special Commissioner Huang praised you.
If you ask me,
let's go have a big meal tonight
to celebrate.
Captain Jiang,
hurry back to the police station.
Someone from the higher-ups is here.
Today is a good day.
I'm here to be a witness.
From today on,
the Fenghuang Police Department and the British Concession Police
officially make peace.
Thank you, Mr. Huo,
for stepping in as a peacemaker.
Being a peacemaker is too tiring.
If it weren't for
Mayor Zeng coming to my residence in person...
I had to give him some face,
right?
Especially since
your Chief Inspector Zhu
is an old acquaintance of mine,
right,
Superintendent Li?
Yes, yes, yes.
Superintendent Li.
I'm sorry about what happened last time.
What happened?
I've forgotten all about it.
Inspector Jiang.
No,
Deputy Chief Jiang.
We meet again.
Inspector Zhou,
how do you have time today
to visit our Fenghuang Police Department?
Officer Huo,
if you can visit friends at my place,
can't I come here?
Welcome, welcome.
All police officers are one family.
Inspector Jiang,
you always see the big picture.
Look, I almost forgot
such an important matter.
Today, entrusted by Mayor Zeng,
I officially announce that
from now on,
Inspector Zhou Wei.
Present!
Under the orders of the British Concession Police,
together with the Fenghuang Police Department,
you will jointly investigate the Jingxiang Society's xenophobia case.
Yes, sir.
It's getting late.
I have matters to attend to at home.
Inspector Jiang,
I'll take my leave now.
You guys talk.
Goodbye.
Farewell, Mr. Huo.
Stop right there.
I was wondering who it was.
So it's you,
the banana, yellow on the outside and white on the inside.
Officer Huo.
You really have a knack
for making cynical remarks.
Enough.
Since we are going to cooperate,
let's talk about the case.
Is there anything you need help with?
What we need to do right now
is to catch Qian Yanqing.
Since it's a joint investigation,
we will also send a representative to assist you.
Then,
we'll send Officer Huo Yining
to assist you with the investigation.
Who are you looking for?
Hello, we are police officers from the Fenghuang Police Department.
We heard that the master of the Jingxiang Society
is preaching here.
We'd like to ask a few questions.
How do I know you are from the police department?
Ask whatever you want.
What does this master look like?
I haven't seen this master's true face.
He's about thirty years old.
He has a local accent.
How long has it been since you saw this master?
The last time the master came
was about a month ago.
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
I think you're
just full of hot air,
bragging.
Then you're just biting off more than you can chew.
Just wait to be proven wrong.
Watch out!
I didn't mean it.
Pervert!
I was protecting you.
You took advantage of me and still act innocent, huh?
Whoever wants to take advantage of you can go ahead.
I certainly don't want to.
Saving my life
is a blessing earned by your ancestors.
You should be thankful.
You!
Let's go.